Register to The Kay Swift Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, 1911-1986; Series I; 4.6' (11 boxes)
  - Stage Works, I.A
    - [Sarah was there. Napoleon song] The Napoleon song., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
      Lacks lyric.
    - [Sarah was there. Preparations for Donna Sarah's entrance] Preparation for Donna Sarah's entrance - to be interrupted. (and for possible use elsewhere, under scene), 1 manuscript piano score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - [Sarah was there. Sarah was there] Verse: "Sarah was there" / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
      Cover in pencil.
    - [Sarah was there. Sarah was there] Refrain: "Sarah was there" / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
    - [Sarah was there. Vienna] Waltz (Vienna), 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 157)
      Lacks lyrics (see 14/62).
    - [Spring again], 1 vocal score (various pagings); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 158)
      Conflation of copyist's manuscript (photostat), Kay Swift's manuscript in ink (annotations in ink), and printed music.
      Arrangement by Deems Taylor of music by Puccini, with lyrics by Kay Swift.
      Numbering of pieces is inconsistent and conflicting.
      A possible order, observed here, is suggested by the annotated script (14/64).
      Contents: Waiters have a wonderful time (4 p.). You're impossible to please (5 p.). Once in a dream world (7 p.). Lonely (7 p., 2 copies). Call it love (6 p.). I'd forgotten (7 p.). [Order unknown or not listed in script, in alphabetical order: Maurice's air "To an Alley cat" (4 p.). Third act ballet (15 p.). Twilight is falling (Kay Swift's manuscript) (7 p.). Without a guiding star (5 p.)]
    - [What if I should haunt you with a minor strain] What if I should haunt you with a minor strain? / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 159)
      Music also set to lyric entitled "When You Hear This Music Remember Me" (see next entry)
      There are 3 versions of the proposal for this work in 14/73: What if I should haunt you with a minor strain?: music and lyrics by Kay Swift -- When you hear this music, remember me: music by Kay Swift; lyrics by Ralph Freed (2 versions [on 2 manuscripts: Pantomime-ballet])
    - [What if I should haunt you with a minor strain] When you hear this music (remember me) / music by Kay Swift; lyric by Ralph Freed., 1 manuscript vocal score (7 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 159)
      Music is also set to lyric entitled "What If I Should Haunt You With a Minor Strain?" (see previous entry)
    - [What if I should haunt you with a minor strain] When you hear this music., 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Individual Songs, I.B
    - [Beautiful time]
      See [One last look] (7/203)
    - [Bee song] The bee song / lyrics by Carolyn Kramer; music by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - [Bee song], 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 29 cm. (Box 6, Folder 160)
    - [Bee song], 1 manuscript vocal score (9 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 160)
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 9.
      First line:...lived there in B's flat for the rest of their life.
    - [Bee song (Sketches)], 4 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 160)
      1 page dated: 6/20/'76.
      1 page dated: 6/18/1976; 6/17/1976; 6/20/76.
    - [Birthday songs], 6 p. of music; 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 161)
      Note at top of 1 p.: For Andy: Sept.29.'41.
      Three songs written for the birthdays of Andrea Kaufman, one of Kay Swift and James Warburg's three daughters; John van Nostrand Dorr; and Mary Hasker, a friend of Kay Swift.
    - [Boots] Boots / words by Rudyard Kipling; Katharine Faulkner Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 34 cm. (Box 6, Folder 162)
      Note at top of page 1: To Mr. Arthur Johnstone.
      Dated: Sept. 3, 1911.
    - [Boots] Boots / words by Rudyard Kipling; music by [K. F. Swift (crossed out)] Katharine Faulkner Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 35 cm. (Box 6, Folder 162)
    - [The circus is a fam'ly affair] The circus is a fam'ly affair / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 163)
      Holograh in ink.
    - [The circus is a fam'ly affiar] The circus is a fam'ly affair., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 163)
    - [The circus is a fam'ly affair] The circus is a fam'ly affair., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 164)
      Incomplete, lacks text and all after p. 2.
    - [The circus is a fam'ly affair] The circus is a fam'ly affair / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (7 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 164)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 7.
      2 copies (1 complete photocopy, annotations in ink)
    - [The circus is a fam'ly affair], 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 164)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1-4 and all after p. 5.
    - [The circus is a fam'ly affair (Sketches)], 6 leaves of music; various sizes. (Box 6, Folder 165)
      1 page dated: 7/13/74.
      1 page dated: 7/14/74.
    - [Corny, but nice] Corny, but nice / music and lyrics Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 166)
      Note at top of page 1: FIRST PIANO COPY. USED IN TORONTO. SEE ENVELOPE MARKED ORIGINAL COPY, NEG. + PHOTOPRINT.
    - [Corny, but nice] Corny, but nice / music and lyric by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 33 cm. (Box 6, Folder 166)
      Holograph (photostat)
    - [Corny, but nice] Corny, but nice / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 166)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in ink.
      At top: Lead sheet.
    - [The dark wind plays a lovely tune] The dark wind plays a lonely tune / lyric by Kay Swift; music by Spanish composer., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 167)
      The composer is Roger Machado.
    - [The dark wind plays a lonely tune] The dark wind plays a lonely tune / by Roger Machado; original Spanish text Leyenda de la Petenera; English lyrics by Kay Swift -- New York: Ricordi, 1953., 1 vocal score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - [The diet song] The diet song / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 168)
    - [Ding-dong-a ding-dong] Ding-dong-a ding-dong / Kay Swift, 1 manuscript chorus score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 169)
      Includes piano accompaniment.
      Dated: June 24.
    - [Doggie]
      See [Songs. Selections] (8/236)
    - [Every time a star falls] Every time a star falls / lyric - Ralph Freed., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 170)
      Unidentified sketches at top and on verso.
      Sketch for "Now and Always" at bottom.
    - [Fighting on the home-front wins] Fighting on the home-front wins., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 171)
    - [Five o'clock feelin's] The five o'clock feelin's., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 172)
      Incomplete, lacks all after p. 4.
    - [Flowering tree] Flowering tree., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 173)
    - [Fountain of youth] The fountain of youth / music by Roger Machado; lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 174)
      Manuscript in Kay Swift's hand in pencil.
    - [Four young fellers on a holiday] Four young fellers on a holiday., 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 175)
    - [Fresh woods and pastures new] Fresh woods and pastures new., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 176)
    - [Fresh woods and pastures new (Sketches)]
      See also [One last look] (7/203)
    - [God is our refuge] God is our refuge / music by [B.F. Seale (erased)], 1 manuscript chorus score (17 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 177)
      3 copies (2 photocopy, 1 annotated in red pencil)
      At top of 1 photocopy: Music by B.F. Seale.
      Pasted onto 1 photocopy: Kay Swift.
      Found in envelope marked: Original (repro paper) and [2 (crossed out)] 3 copies (1 copy at office-4/28/64) of Psalm 46 ("God Is My Refuge") for 5 voices, a capella Kay Swift (Pseudonym "B.F. Seale" is on the music, as it was needed for contest March 1, '63) School of Music Syracuse University Syracuse 10, N.Y.
    - [God is our refuge] God is our refuge / music by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript chorus score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 178)
    - [God is our refuge (Sketches)], 6 leaves of music; 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 179)
      "Ps. 149 March 3".
    - [Great big piece of chalk] "Chalk" / Mel Howard; Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 180)
    - [Great big piece of chalk], 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 180)
      Page 2 contains sketch for lyric and unidentified musical sketches.
    - [Great big piece of chalk] A great big piece of chalk / words by Mel Howard; music by Kay Swift -- London: Peter Maurice, 1958., 1 vocal score (3 p.); 28 cm. (Box 6, Folder 180)
      See also [There's no escape] (8/240)
    - [Happiest pair in town (Sketches)], 1 leaf of music; 32 cm. (Box 6, Folder 181)
      At top: Patter for "Happiest Pair In Town."
    - [Happy new year] Happy new year / lyrics-Freed; music-Swift., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 31 cm. (Box 6, Folder 182)
    - [I bought a horse in Saratoga], 1 manuscript piano part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 183)
      Note at bottom: Incomplete - End of "I bought a horse in Saratoga."
    - [I hate the bard], 1 manuscript vocal score (8 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 184)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1-2 and all after p. 8.
      Lyrics by Kay Swift and Hunter Galloway (see complete lyric in 15/438)
    - [I want something grand] I want something grand., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 34 cm. (Box 7, Folder 185)
      At top of page 1: Chorus.
    - [I want something grand] I want something grand., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 34 cm. (Box 7, Folder 185)
      Vocal line lacks most text.
    - [I'd walk a mile for you] I'd walk a mile for you / lyrics by Al Silverman [i.e., Stillman]; music by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 186)
      Holograph (?) in ink, annotations in pencil.
      Stamped on all p: MUSIC LIBRARY ARNOLD JOHNSON.
      2 copies (1 negative photostat)
      Photostat found with "A Little Bit of Independence" (see entry under Music by Other Composers) and letter in folder marked: Photostat of "I'd Walk A Mile For You" by K.S. + Al Stillman plus letter to people who stole (consciously or not) the song + published it.
      "A Little Bit of Independence" and correspondence laid in.
      Al Stillman was staff lyricist at Radio City Music Hall.
      Written for Radio City, ca. 1935.
    - [I'm all washed up with love] I'm all washed up with love / by Swift + Silverman [i.e., Stillman]; arr. Moss., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 28 cm. (Box 7, Folder 187)
      Includes instrumental cues.
    - [Impression Fausse] Impression Fausse (dance souris trotte); Paul Verlaine; Katharine Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 34 cm. (Box 7, Folder 188)
    - [Jerusalem, Jerusalem (Sketches)] Jerusalem, Jerusalem., 1 leaf of music: 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 189)
    - [Kitty]
    - [Let's take a walk around the west branch] Let's take a walk around the west branch / Kay Swift, 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - [Little church around the corner] Little church around the corner / by Swift- Stillman., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 191)
      Copyist's manuscript in pencil, annotations in ink and red pencil.
      At top of page 1: Joyce and....
    - [Little church around the corner] The little church around the corner / [music] by Kay Swift + A. Silverman [i.e., Stillman], 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 191)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 2-4.
    - [Little church around the corner], 1 manuscript chorus (19 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 192)
      Copyist's manuscript (photocopy), annotations in pencil, blue pencil, and ink.
      At top of p. 17: Duet version.
      Stamped at bottom of p. 17 and 18: RADIO CITY MUSIC HALL.
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 17.
    - [Little church around the corner] Lyric Al Stillman; tune Kay Swift., 1 manuscript part (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 192)
    - [Little friend], 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 193)
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1.
      First line:...friend, your day is still far away.
    - [Long run] The long run., 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - [Long run] The long run., 2 manuscript parts (1 p., 1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 194)
      Unidentified sketches on verso of 1 manuscript (dated: Dec. 8, 12.25 a.m.)
    - [Man, have pity on man] Man, have pity on man / music by Kay Swift; orchestrated by Don Rose; text by - Ursula Vaughn [sic] - Williams, from - "Noah's ark.", 1 manuscript score (11 p.); 44 cm. (Box 26, Folder 717)
      On cover: "Man, have pity on man" Music by Kay Swift Long score, orchestrated by Don Rose Poem by Ursula Vaughn [sic] Williamanuscript
      Dated: Sept. 25, 1970.
    - [Man, have pity on man] Man, have pity on man / music by Kay Swift; text by Ursula [Vaughn (crossed out)] Vaughan Williams, from "Noah's ark.", 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 195)
      Holograph (photocopy), annotations in pencil, red pencil, and ink.
      Dated: 1972.
    - [Man, have pity on man] Man, have pity on man / music by Kay Swift; poem by Ursula Vaugn [sic] Williams., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 195)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in blue ink and pasted in.
      Text in blue ink.
      Incomplete, lacks p. 3.
      2 copies (1 complete photocopy).
    - [Man, have pity on man], 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 195)
      Holograph in black and blue ink.
      Incomplete, lacks p. 1 and all after p. 3.
      See also [Shoana] (8/233)
    - [Marcelle knows best] Marcelle knows best., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 196)
      Part for chorus.
    - [The Michigan band] The Michigan band., 1 manuscript score (5 p.); 36 cm. (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - [The Michigan band], 1 manuscript condensed score (16 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 197)
      Incomplete, lacks all before p. 12 and after p. 16.
    - [The most beautiful time of the year] The most beautiful time of the year / Kay Swift; lyrics-Ralph Freed., 1 manuscript piano score (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 198)
      Unidentified sketches on verso.
      Written possibly for proposed musical Here's the Pitch (see 13/34).
    - [The most beautiful time of the year] The most beautiful time of the year / Swift; Freed., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 198)
    - [My thoughts are like the little birds] My thoughts are like the little birds / text by Grace H. Duffield; music by Katharine Faulkner Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 7, Folder 199)
    - [Nice to be nice]
      See [Write a song for me (Sketches)] (9/264)
    - [Nihil] Nihil., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 34 cm. (Box 7, Folder 200)
    - [Now and always] Now and always / music and lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 201)
    - [Now and always (Sketches)]
      See [Every time a star falls] (6/170)
    - [One last look] One last look / lyrics and music by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 202)
    - [One last look] One last look / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 202)
      Holograph (?) in ink, annotations in pencil and ink.
    - [One last look] One last look., 1 manuscript vocal score (1 p.); 30 cm. (Box 7, Folder 202)
      Incomplete, contains first 3 measures only, and lacks text.
    - [One last look] One last look., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 203)
      Incomplete, contains verse only, and lacks text.
    - [One last look] One last look / Kay Swift, 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 203)
      Partially texted.
    - [One last look] On last look / Kay Swift (music and lyrics), 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 203)
      Verso contains verse to "Beautiful Time."
    - [One last look (Sketches)], 1 leaf of music; 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 203)
      At top: Verse to "One Last Look."
      Includes sketches for "Fresh Woods and Pastures" and "Parents."
    - [Parents] Parents., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - [Parents (Sketches)]
      See [One Last Look] (7/203)
    - [Piggie]
    - [Prayer with a beat] Prayer with a beat / music and lyric Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 205)
      Note on p. 4: FRED AHLERT 1619 B'WAY.
    - [Prayer with a beat] Prayer with a beat / music and lyrics: Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - [Prayer with a beat] Prayer with a beat / music ... lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript part (1 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - [Poems in praise of practically nothing] Poems in praise of practically nothing (five excepts) / Samuel Hoffenstein; Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (12 p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 206)
    - [Poems in praise of practically nothing] Poems in praise of practically nothing / Samuel Hoffenstein; Kay Swift., 2 manuscript parts (3 p., 3 p.); 32 cm., 35 cm. (Box 7, Folder 206)
    - [Psalm 47 (Sketches)], 1 page of music; 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 207)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring] Reaching for the brass ring / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript score (120 P.); various sizes. (Box 7, Folder 208)
      Copyist's manuscript (possibly holograph) in pencil, annotations in red pencil and ink.
      Contents: Reaching for the brass ring. Smiling Betsy. John likes it when the wind blows. Upside down. I've got a horse. The sleepy song. My teeny restaurant. Bath time. Ridin' his bike.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring], 156 manuscript parts; 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 209-217)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil, red and blue pencil, ink, and pasted in.
      Parts for score in 7/208.
      Inventory lists found with parts laid in.
      Some 2 copies (1 photocopy, some annotated).
      Contents: Bath time. I've got a horse. John likes it when the wind blows. My teeny restaurant. Reaching for the brass ring. Ridin' his bike. The sleepy song. Smiling Betsy. Upside down.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring] I've got a horse / Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript condensed score ([58] p.); 32 cm. (Box 7, Folder 218)
      Copyist's manuscript in ink, annotations in pencil, red and blue pencil, and pasted in.
      Condensed score of 7/208.
      Photostats found in envelope marked: MASTER NEGATIVES "BRASS RING" (9 SONGS) (CONDUCTOR'S SCORES) NOTE: THE SONGS ARE NOW IN ORDER FOR PURPOSE OF MAKING COPIES IN THE FUTURE. THEY ARE NUMBERED FROM 1 TO 57. ALSO, MAESTROSTAT SPECIAL TRANSPARENCY MASTER COPIES.
      Contents: I've got a horse. Upside down. Ridin' his bike. My teeny restaurant. John likes it when the wind blows. Smiling Betsy. Bath time. The sleepy song. Reaching for the brass ring.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Bath time] Bath time / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Bath time] Bath time / music + lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 219)
      Holograph (photostat), annotations in pencil.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Bath time] Bath time / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 28 cm. (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. I've got a horse] I've got a horse / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 31 cm. (Box 8, Folder 220)
      Holograph (negative photostat), annotations in white ink.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. John likes it when the wind blows] John likes it when the wind blows / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 29 cm. (Box 8, Folder 221)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. John likes it when the wind blows] John likes it when the wind blows / music and lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 221)
      Holograph (photostat), annotations in pencil and red pencil.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. My teeny restaurant] My teeny restaurant / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 222)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. My teeny restaurant] My teeny restaurant / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 31 cm. (Box 8, Folder 222)
      Holograph (photostat), annotations in red pencil, ink, and pasted in.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. My teeny restaurant] My teeny restaurant / music and lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 222)
      Holograph in ink, annotations in red pencil.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Rachel is the singing one] Rachel is the singing one / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (2 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 223)
      Not in orchestrated version in 7/208.
      "Kay Swift: Civilized Pleasure" (Stereo Review, December 1975, p. 108) indicates this song was added to Reaching for the Brass Ring.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Rachel is the singing one], 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 223)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Reaching for the brass ring] Reaching for the brass ring / music and lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 224)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Ridin' his bike] Ridin' his bike / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Ridin' his bike] Ridin' his bike / Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal. score (4 p.); 29 cm. (Box 8, Folder 225)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Sleepy song] The sleepy song / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Sleepy song] The sleepy song / music and lyrics Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 226)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Sleepy song] The sleepy song / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 30 cm. (Box 8, Folder 226)
      Holograph (photostat), annotations in pencil, red pencil, ink, and pasted in.
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Smiling Betsy] Smiling Betsy / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal score (5 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Smiling Betsy] Smiling Betsy / music and lyrics by Kay Swift., 1 manuscript vocal. score (6 p.); 28 cm. (Box 8, Folder 227)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Three balloons] Three balloons / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P. A.G.A.C., 1 manuscript vocal score (4 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 228)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Three balloons] Three balloons / music and lyrics by Kay Swift A.S.C.A.P., 1 manuscript vocal score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 228)
      Holograph (negative photostat)
    - [Reaching for the brass ring. Three balloons, arr.] Three balloons., 1 manuscript score (3 p.); 32 cm. (Box 8, Folder 228)
      Arr. for: clarinet and piano
      [Reaching for the brass ring. Three balloons, arr.
      Three balloons.
      1 manuscript score ( 2 p. + 1 p.); 41 cm.
      Arr. for: flute, oboe, clarinet I, clarinet II, bassoon, horn I, horn II, percussion, violoncello, voice, violin I, violin II, viola, violoncello, and double bass.
      Incomplete, lacks all but p. 1-2 and 1 p.